ANDRII SUSHKET

Senior Front End Engineer

📞 +352661527603 🔘 andy.sushket@gmail.com 🗳 linkedin.com/in/andrii-sushket 🔍 Luxembourg

SUMMARY

Experienced Frontend Engineer with 7 years of expertise, passionate about tackling challenges and solving complex problems. Previously contributed to 3D warehouse solutions at Logivations and currently focused on solar panel visualization projects at Svitla Systems. Actively working on building a new core for rooftop solar panel visualization using advanced tools and technologies.

Experienced in JS, TS, React, Redux, Three.js, MongoDB and more. An adaptable team player. Eager to expand 3D knowledge and dive into C++ and Unreal Engine. Future-focused and ready for new adventures.

SKILLS

JavaScript		Three.js		React	
Redux	Nex	t.js	GLSL		
Typescript (GSAP	AP Blender		
HTML	CSS	CSS Backbone			
Reflux	Sag	a (GIT	-	
jQuery	MongoDB			Node.js	
PHP	Socke	t.io	SC)L	
Unreal Engine					

LANGUAGES

English	Advanced
Ukrainian	Native
Russian	Native
Luxembourgish	Beginner
French	Beginner
Spanish	Beginner

EXPERIENCE

Senior Front End Engineer

Svitla Systems

iii 10/2021 - Present ♀ Remote, Luxembourg

- Developed a new rendering engine using Three.js, resulting in a tenfold increase in performance
- Implemented synchronization between 3D objects and Google Maps tiles, ensuring interaction
- Built-in support for quad trees to optimize interactive operations such as intersection and selection
- Optimized processes at the shader level to improve rendering performance Three.is
- Stack: JavaScript, Three.js, React, Redux, Saga, Node.js, MongoDB, and Socket.io

WebGL developer

Logivations

ii 10/2017 - 10/2021 **Q** Lviv, Ukraine

- Developed real-time visualizations, collaborating with ML for object detection and management
- Revamped product packaging visualization, improving functionality and performance
- Developed support for importing animated models, ensuring JSON data storage in the database
- Stack: JavaScript, TypeScript, Three.js, React, Redux, Reflux, Backbone, and Socket.io

Front-end developer

CBA Hosting

- Improved page load times by optimizing frontend code for the hosting page
- · Worked with templates on the PHP side
- · Added new features and animations
- Stack: JavaScript, PHP, jQuery, HTML, CSS

EDUCATION

Radio communication, broadcasting and television - Specialist

Polytechnic University

= 2014 - 2016 **♥** Lviv

Radio engineering - Bachelor

Polytechnic University

= 2009 - 2014 **♀** Lviv

TRAINING / COURSES

Unreal Engine 5 Three.js

Udemy Three.js Journey

JavaScript HTML/CSS

Logos IT Academy Logos IT Academy